<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!-- Meson Build -->
  <id>de.haeckerfelix.Shortwave</id>
  <name>Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">短波</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Sóng ngắn</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Коротка хвиля</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kratki valovi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Rövidhullám</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">शॉर्टवेव</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">موج کوتاه</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Shortwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Shortwave</name>
  <translation type="gettext">shortwave</translation>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">de.haeckerfelix.Shortwave.desktop</launchable>
  <!-- General -->
  <summary>Listen to internet radio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">收聽網路電臺</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">收听互联网广播</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Nghe đài phát qua mạng internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Прослуховування інтернет-радіо</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">İnternet radyolarını dinle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Lyssna på internetradio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Слушајте радио преко Интернета</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Poslušanje spletnih radijskih postaj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Počúvajte internetové rádiá</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Слушайте интернет-радио</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Ascultați la stația de radio prin internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Ouça a rádios da Internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ouça rádio na Internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Słuchanie radia internetowego</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Escotar la ràdio Internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Beluister internetradio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ინტერნეტ რადიოს მოსმენა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Ascoltare radio su Internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Hlusta á internet-útvarp</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Dengarkan radio internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Ascolta le radio per internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Internetes rádió hallgatása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Slušajte internetski radio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">इंटरनेट रेडियो सुनें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">האזנה לתחנת רדיו</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Escoitar radio por internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Scolte la internet-radio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Écouter une radio internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kuuntele internetradiota</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">شنیدن رادیوهای اینترنتی</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Entzun interneteko irrratiak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Escuchar la radio por Internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Listen to internet radio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ακρόαση ιντερνετικού ραδιοφώνου</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Internetradio hören</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Lyt til internetradio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Poslouchejte internetové rádio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Escolta la ràdio per internet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Радио по Интернет</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Слухайце інтэрнэт-радыё</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Shortwave is an internet radio player that provides access to a station database with over 50,000 stations.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">短波是个提供对具有超过 50000 个电台的电台数据库访问的互联网广播播放器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">«Коротка хвиля» — програвач інтернет-радіостанцій, який надає доступ до бази з понад 50000 станцій.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Shortwave, 50.000’i aşkın istasyon barındıran veri tabanına erişmenizi sağlayan internet radyo oynatıcısıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Shortwave är en internetradiospelare som ger tillgång till en stationsdatabas med över 50000 stationer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program Kratki valovi je internetni radijski predvajalnik, ki omogoča dostop do podatkovne zbirke več kot 50.000 postaj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Shortwave - это интернет-радиоплеер, который предоставляет доступ к базе данных станций, насчитывающей более 50 000 станций.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Shortwave é um reprodutor de rádio na Internet que fornece acesso a um banco de dados de estações com mais de 50.000 estações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Shortwave es un lector de ràdio internet que provesís accès a una basa de donadas d'estacions amb mai de 50 000 estacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Shortwave ინტერნეტ-რადიოს დამკვრელია, რომელიც საშუალებას გაძლევთ 50, 000-ზე მეტ სადგურს მოუსმინოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Shortwave è un riproduttore di radio su Internet che fornisce l'accesso a un database con oltre 50.000 stazioni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Shortwave es un reproductor de radio per internet que forni accesso a un base de datos con plus de 30.000 stationes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Shortwave הוא נגן רדיו אינטרנט המספק גישה למסד נתונים עם למעלה מ־50,000 תחנות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Shortwave est un lecteur de radios internet qui permet d’accéder à une base de données de plus de 50 000 stations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Shortwave on internetradioasemien toistamiseen tarkoitettu sovellus, joka tarjoaa yli 50 000 aseman tietokannan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">موج کوتاه پخش‌کنندهٔ رادیو اینترنتی‌ای است که دسترسی به پایگاه داده‌ای با بیش از ۵۰٫۰۰۰ ایستگاه را فراهم می‌کند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Shortwave interneteko irrati-estazioen erreproduzigailua da, 50.000 estazio baino gehiago dituen datu-base baterako sarbidea ematen duena.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Shortwave es un reproductor de radio por Internet que proporciona acceso a una base de datos con más de 50.000 emisoras.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Shortwave ist eine Internetradio-Wiedergabe, die Zugang zu einer Senderdatenbank mit über 50.000 Sendern bietet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Shortwave er en internetradioafspiller, som giver adgang til en database med over 50.000 stationer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Shortwave е интернет радио плеър с база от данни от над 50 000 станции.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Shortwave — гэта прайгравальнік інтэрнэт-радыё з доступам да базы даных, якая змяшчае больш за 50 000 станцый.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">特色：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">特性：</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Các tính năng:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Funcționalități:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Funkcje:</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Foncionalitats :</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Functies:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Eiginleikar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Functionalitates:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Značajke:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">विशेषताएं:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">תכונות:</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Funzionalitâts:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">ویژگی‌ها:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Eginbideak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Функции:</p>
    <p xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Магчымасці:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Create your own library where you can add your favorite stations</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">將您喜愛的電臺加入您的專屬電臺庫</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">创建您自己的媒体库，可以在其中添加最喜欢的电台</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Tạo thư viện của riêng bạn, nơi bạn có thể thêm các đài yêu thích của mình</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створіть власну бібліотеку, до якої ви зможете додавати улюблені станції</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Beğendiğiniz istasyonları ekleyerek kendi kitaplığınızı oluşturun</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skapa ditt eget bibliotek där du kan lägga till dina favoritstationer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Направите сопствену библиотеку у коју можете додати ваше омиљене станице</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ustvarite svojo zbirko, v katero lahko dodate vse priljubljene postaje</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytvorte svoju vlastnú knižnicu, do ktorej si môžete pridať obľúbené stanice</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Создайте собственную библиотеку, в которую можно добавлять любимые станции</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Creați-vă propria bibliotecă unde puteți adăuga stațiile favorite</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Crie sua própria biblioteca à qual você pode adicionar suas estações favoritas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criar sua própria coleção onde pode adicionar suas estações favoritas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie własnej kolekcji, do której można dodawać ulubione stacje</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Creatz vòstra pròpria bibliotèca ont podètz apondre vòstras estacions favoritas</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Maak uw eigen collectie aan en voeg uw favoriete radiostations eraan toe</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">შექმენით თქვენი საკუთარი ბიბლიოთეკა, სადაც შეგიძლიათ თქვენი საყვარელი სადგურები დაამატოთ</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creare una propria raccolta dove poter aggiungere le stazioni preferite</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Búðu til eigin lista sem þú getur bætt í uppáhalds-stöðvunum þínum</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Buat perpustakaan Anda sendiri di mana Anda dapat menambahkan stasiun favorit Anda</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Crea tu proprie bibliotheca ubi tu pote adder tu stationes favorite</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Saját könyvtár létrehozása, ahol hozzáadhatja a kedvenc állomásait</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Stvorite svoju vlastitu radioteku gdje možete dodati svoje omiljene stanice</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">अपनी खुद की लाइब्रेरी बनाएं जहां आप अपने पसंदीदा स्टेशन जोड़ सकें</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">יצירת ספרייה משלך אליה ניתן להוסיף את התחנות המועדפות עליך</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Cree a súa propia biblioteca onde engadir as súas emisoras favoritas</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Creâ la tô librarie personâl, dulà che tu puedis zontâ lis tôs stazions preferidis</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Créez votre propre bibliothèque où ajouter vos stations préférées</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Luo oma kirjasto, johon voit lisätä omat suosikkiasemasi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">ایجاد کتاب‌خانهٔ خودتان با توانایی افزودن ایستگاه‌های محبوبتان</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Sortu zure liburutegi propioa zure gogoko estazioak gehitzeko</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Crear su propia biblioteca donde puede añadir sus emisoras favoritas</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Create your own library where you can add your favourite stations</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Δημιουργήστε τη δική σας βιβλιοθήκη όπου μπορείτε να προσθέσετε τους αγαπημένους σας σταθμούς</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Erstellen Sie Ihre eigene Bibliothek, zu der Sie Ihre Lieblingssender hinzufügen</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Opret dit eget bibliotek hvor du kan tilføje dine favoritstationer</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Vytvoření vlastní knihovny, kam si můžete přidat oblíbené stanice</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Crea la teva pròpia biblioteca on pots afegir les teves emissores preferides</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Може да създадете собствена библиотека, в която да добавите любимите си станции</li>
      <li xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Стварыце ўласную бібліятэку, куды будзеце дадаваць свае ўлюбёныя станцыі</li>
      <li>Easily search and discover new radio stations</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">輕而易舉便能搜尋與探索新電臺</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">轻松搜索并发现新电台</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Dễ dàng tìm kiếm và khám phá các đài phát thanh mới</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Простий пошук і виявлення нових радіостанцій</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yeni radyo istasyonlarını kolayca arayın ve keşfedin</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sök och upptäck enkelt nya radiostationer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Једноставна претрага и откривање нових радио станица</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Enostavno iskanje in odkrivanje novih radijskih postaj</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Jednoducho vyhľadávajte a objavujte nové rádiové stanice</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Легкий поиск и открытие новых радиостанций</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Căutați și descoperiți stații noi radio cu ușurință</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquise e descubra facilmente novas estações de rádio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar facilmente e descobrir novas estações de rádio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Łatwe wyszukiwanie i odkrywanie nowych stacji radiowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Cercatz e descobrissètz aisidament de novèlas estacions de ràdio</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoek en ontdek eenvoudig nieuwe radiostations</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მარტივად მოძებნეთ და აღმოაჩინეთ ახალი რადიოსადგურები</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cercare e scoprire facilmente nuove stazioni radio</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Uppgötvaðu og leitaðu á auðveldan máta að nýjum útvarpsstöðvum</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mudah mencari dan menemukan stasiun radio baru</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Cerca e discoperi nove stationes de radio facilemente</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Új rádióállomások egyszerű keresése és felfedezése</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Jednostavno pretražujte i otkrijte nove radio stanice</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">नए रेडियो स्टेशन आसानी से खोजें और ढूंढें</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">חיפוש קל לגילוי תחנות רדיו חדשות</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Busque e descubra facilmente novas emisoras de radio</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Cirî e scuvierzi cun facilitât lis gnovis stazions radio</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Cherchez et découvrez de nouvelles stations de radio</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Etsi ja löydä vaivatta uusia radioasemia</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">جست‌وجو و کشف آسان ایستگاه‌های رادیویی جدید</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bilatu eta aurkitu irrati-estazio berriak modu errazean</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Buscar y descubrir nuevas emisoras de radio fácilmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Easily search and discover new radio stations</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εύκολη αναζήτηση και ανακάλυψη νέων ραδιοφωνικών σταθμών</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einfaches Suchen und Entdecken neuer Radiosender</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Det er let at søge efter og opdage nye radiostationer</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Snadné vyhledávání a objevování nových rádiových stanic</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerca fàcilment i descobreix emissores de ràdio noves</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Лесно търсене и откриване на нови радиостанции</li>
      <li xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Просты пошук і агляд новых радыёстанцый</li>
      <li>Automatic recognition of tracks, with the possibility to save them individually</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">自动识别音轨，并可以将其分别保存</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне виявлення пісень із можливістю їхнього збереження окремо</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Parçaları kendiliğinden tanıma, ayrı ayrı kaydetme özelliği</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk igenkänning av spår, med möjligheten att spara dem individuellt</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Samodejno prepoznavanje skladb z možnostjo posamičnega shranjevanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Reconhecimento automático de faixas, com a possibilidade de salvá-las individualmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Reconeissença automatica de las pistas, amb la possibilitat de las enregistrar individualament</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">სიმღერების ავტომატური ამოცნობა, მათი ინდივიდუალურად შენახვის შესაძლებლობით</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Riconoscere automaticamente i brani con la possibilità di salvarli individualmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Recognoscentia automatic de cantos, con le possibilitate de salvar los individualmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">זיהוי אוטומטי של רצועות, עם אפשרות לשמור אותן בנפרד</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Reconnaissance automatique des pistes, avec possibilité de les enregistrer individuellement</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kappaleiden automaattinen tunnistaminen ja mahdollisuus tallentaa yksittäisiä kappaleita</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">بازشناسی خودکار قطعه‌ها با امکان ذخیرهٔ جداگانه‌شان</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Pisten ezagutze automatikoa, haiek banaka gordetzeko aukerarekin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Reconocimiento automático de las canciones, con la posibilidad de guardarlas individualmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Erkennung von Titeln, mit der Möglichkeit, sie einzeln zu speichern</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Automatisk genkendelse af lydspor med mulighed for at gemme dem enkeltvis</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Автоматично разпознаване на песните с възможност да ги запазите индивидуално</li>
      <li>Responsive application layout, compatible for small and large screens</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">響應式程式佈局，不論熒幕尺寸大小皆可相容</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">响应式应用程序布局，兼容小型屏幕和大型屏幕</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Bố cục ứng dụng thích ứng, tương thích với cả màn hình nhỏ và lớn</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Якісне компонування вікна програми, яке сумісне із малими і великими екранами</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Küçük ve büyük ekranlarla uyumlu, duyarlı uygulama düzeni</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kvickt reagerande programlayout, kompatibel med små och stora skärmar</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Изглед програма прилагодљив величини екрана, усклађен са малим и великим екранима</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Odzivno prilagajanje programa je skladno z velikimi in majhnimi zasloni</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Dobre reagujúce rozloženie aplikácie, kompatibilné s malými aj veľkými obrazovkami</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Отзывчивый интерфейс приложения, совместимый с маленькими и большими экранами</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Aspect de aplicație responsiv, compatibil cu ecrane mici și mari</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Leiaute de aplicativo responsivo, compatível com telas pequenas e grandes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Modelo de aplicação responsivo, compatível com ecrãs pequenos ou grandes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Interfejs zgodny z małymi i wielkimi ekranami</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Disposicion d'aplicacion responsiva, compatibla amb d'ecrans pichons e grands</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Responsieve indeling, geschikt voor zowel kleine als grote schermen</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აპლიკაციის მოხერხებული განლაგება, თავსებადი მცირე და დიდ ეკრანებთან</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Una reattiva disposizione dell'applicazione, compatibile per schermi piccoli e grandi</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Aðlaganlegt viðmót , samræmanlegt fyrir litla og stóra skjái</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tata letak aplikasi responsif, kompatibel untuk layar kecil dan besar</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Disposition responsive de application, compatibile con schermos parve e grande</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Alkalmazkodó alkalmazáselrendezés, kis és nagy képernyők támogatása</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Odgovarajući izgled aplikacije, kompatibilan za male i velike zaslone</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">उत्तरदायी अनुप्रयोग अभिन्यास, छोटी और बड़ी स्क्रीन के लिए संगत</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">פריסת היישום משתנה ומגיבה, מתאימה למסכים קטנים וגדולים כאחד</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Disposición de aplicación responsiva, compatíbel con pantallas pequenas e grandes</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Struture dal program adatabil, compatibil cui schermis piçui e grancj</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Interface adaptative, compatible avec les petits et grands écrans</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Mukautuva sovelluksen asettelu, yhteensopiva pienien ja suurien näyttöjen kanssa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">چینش واکنشگرای برنامه،‌سازگار با صفحه‌های بزرگ و کوچک</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aplikazio-diseinu moldagarria, pantaila txiki zein handiekin bateragarria dena</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Diseño adaptativo, compatible con pantallas grandes y pequeñas</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Responsive application layout, compatible for small and large screens</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Dynamisches Anwendungslayout, kompatibel mit kleinen und großen Bildschirmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Programlayoutet tilpasser sig automatisk på både små og store skærme</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Responzivní rozvržení aplikace kompatibilní s malými a velkými obrazovkami</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Disposició d'aplicació responsiva, compatible amb pantalles grans i petites</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Потребителски интерфейс съвместим с малки и големи екрани</li>
      <li xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Адаптыўны інтэрфейс праграмы, сумяшчальны з малымі і вялікімі экранамі</li>
      <li>Play audio on supported network devices (e.g. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">在支援的網路裝置上播放音訊（譬如 Google Chromecasts）</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">在受支持的网络设备（例如 Google Chromecasts）上播放音频</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Phát âm thanh trên các thiết bị mạng được hỗ trợ (ví dụ: Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Відтворення звукових даних на підтримуваних пристроях у мережі (наприклад, Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Desteklenen ağ aygıtlarında ses çalma (ör. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spela ljud på nätverksenheter som stöds (t.ex. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Пуштање звука на подржаним мрежним уређајима (нпр.: Гугл Хромкастови)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Predvajanje glasbe na podprtih napravah (npr. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prehrávajte zvuk na podporovaných sieťových zariadeniach (napr. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Воспроизведение аудио на поддерживаемых сетевых устройствах (например, Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Redă audio pe dispozitive de rețea suportate (de ex. Google Chromecasturi)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Reprodução de áudio em dispositivos de rede compatíveis (por exemplo, Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Reproduz som em dispositivos de rede com suporte (ex.: Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzanie dźwięku na obsługiwanych urządzeniach sieciowych (np. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Legir l'àudio sus de periferics de ret preses en carga (per exemple Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Audio afspelen op ondersteunde netwerkapparaten (zoals Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აუდიოს დაკვრა მხარდაჭერილ ქსელურ მოწყობილობებზე (მაგ. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Riprodurre l'audio su dispositivi di rete supportati (esempio: Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Afspilun í nettengdum tækjum (t.d. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Memutar audio pada perangkat jaringan yang didukung (mis. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Reproduce audio sur apparatos de rete supportate (p.e. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Hang lejátszása a támogatott hálózati eszközökön (például Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Reprodukcija zvuka na podržanim mrežnim uređajima (npr. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">समर्थित नेटवर्क उपकरणो पर ऑडियो चलाएं (जैसे Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">ניגון שמע בהתקני רשת נתמכים (למשל Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Reprodución de son en dispositivos de rede compatíbeis (p.ex. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Riprodusi l'audio sui dispositîfs di rêt supuartâts (p.e. i Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Diffusion audio sur les appareils réseau pris en charge (par exemple les Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Toista ääntä tuetuilla verkkolaitteilla (esim. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">پخش صدا روی افزاره‌های شبکه‌ای پشتیبانی شده (مانند پخش کروم‌های گوگل)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Erreproduzitu audioa onartutako sare-gailuetan (adibidez Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Reproducir sonido en dispositivos de red soportados (Ej. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Play audio on supported network devices (e.g. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αναπαραγωγή ήχου σε υποστηριζόμενες συσκευές δικτύου (π.χ. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Tonwiedergabe auf unterstützten Netzwerkgeräten (z. B. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Afspil lyd på understøttede netværksenheder (f.eks. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Přehrávání zvuku na podporovaných síťových zařízeních (např. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Reprodueix àudio en dispositius de xarxa compatibles (p. ex. Google Chromecasts)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Възпроизвеждане през поддържани мрежови устройства (примерно с Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Прайграванне аўдыя на сеткавых прыладах, якія падтрымліваюцца (напр. Google Chromecast)</li>
      <li>Seamless integration into the GNOME desktop environment</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">與 GNOME 桌面環境無縫結合</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">与 GNOME 桌面环境无缝集成</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Tích hợp liên thông vào môi trường máy tính để bàn GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Безшовна інтеграція до стільничного середовища GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">GNOME masaüstü ortamı ile kusursuz tümleşim</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sömlös integration med skrivbordsmiljön GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Ненаметљива усклађеност у Гномово радно окружење</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Popolna vključenost programa v namizno okolje GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hladká integrácia do pracovného prostredia GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Бесшовная интеграция в среду рабочего стола GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Integrare unitară în mediul desktop GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração perfeita no ambiente GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração transparente com o ambiente de trabalho GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Integracja ze środowiskiem GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Integracion transparenta dins l'environament de burèu GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Naadloze integratie in de GNOME-bureaubladomgeving</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">შეუმჩნეველი ინტეგრაცია GNOME-ს გარემოში</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Una perfetta integrazione all'interno dell'ambiente desktop GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Fellur smekklega inn í GNOME gluggaumhverfið</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Integrasi mulus ke dalam lingkungan destop GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Integration sin problemas al ambiente de scriptorio GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Zökkenőmentes integráció a GNOME asztali környezetbe</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Besprijekorna integracija u GNOME radno okruženje</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">गनोम डेस्कटॉप वातावरण में सहज एकीकरण</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">שילוב חלק בסביבת שולחן העבודה GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Integración sen problemas no ambiente de escritorio de GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Integrazion perfete cul ambient di scritori GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégration transparente à l’environnement de bureau GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Saumaton integraatio Gnome-työpöytäympäristöön</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">یکپارچگی با محیط میزکار گنوم</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Josturatik gabeko integrazioa GNOME mahaigaineko ingurunearekin</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración sin fisuras con el entorno de escritorio GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Seamless integration into the GNOME desktop environment</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Απρόσκοπτη ενσωμάτωση στο GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Nahtlose Integration in die GNOME-Arbeitsumgebung</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Perfekt integration i GNOME-skrivebordsmiljøet</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Dokonale zapadne do uživatelského prostředí GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Integració a l'entorn d'escriptori GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Идеална интеграция с GNOME</li>
      <li xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Поўная інтэграцыя ў працоўнае асяроддзе GNOME</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <!-- Branding -->
  <developer_name>Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="vi">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ro">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="oc">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ka">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="is">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ia">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hu">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hi">फेलिक्स हैकर</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="he">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fur">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fa">فلیکس هکر</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="bg">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Фелікс Хекер (Felix Häcker)</developer_name>
  <developer id="de.haeckerfelix">
    <name>Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="vi">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="uk">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="tr">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="sv">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="sl">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="sk">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="ru">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="ro">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="pl">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="oc">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="nl">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="ka">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="it">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="is">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="id">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="ia">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="hu">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="hr">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">फेलिक्स हैकर</name>
    <name xml:lang="he">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="gl">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="fur">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="fr">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="fi">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="fa">فلیکس هکر</name>
    <name xml:lang="eu">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="en-GB">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="el">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="de">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="da">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="cs">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="ca">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="bg">Felix Häcker</name>
    <name xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Фелікс Хекер (Felix Häcker)</name>
  </developer>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#fcd85e</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#865e3c</color>
  </branding>
  <!-- License -->
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <!-- URLs -->
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.gnome.org/Shortwave/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Shortwave/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://liberapay.com/haecker-felix</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.gnome.org/module/Shortwave/</url>
  <url type="contact">https://matrix.to/#/#shortwave:gnome.org</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Shortwave</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://welcome.gnome.org/app/Shortwave/</url>
  <!-- Supported Hardware -->
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <supports>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </supports>
  <!-- Screenshots -->
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Shortwave/raw/main/data/screenshots/1.png</image>
      <caption>Create your own library where you can add your favorite stations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">將您喜愛的電臺加入您的專屬電臺庫</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">创建您自己的媒体库，可以在其中添加最喜欢的电台</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Tạo thư viện của riêng bạn, nơi bạn có thể thêm các đài yêu thích của mình</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Створіть власну бібліотеку, до якої ви зможете додавати улюблені станції</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Beğendiğiniz istasyonları ekleyerek kendi kitaplığınızı oluşturun</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skapa ditt eget bibliotek där du kan lägga till dina favoritstationer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Направите сопствену библиотеку у коју можете додати ваше омиљене станице</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Ustvarite svojo zbirko, v katero lahko dodate vse priljubljene postaje</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Vytvorte svoju vlastnú knižnicu, do ktorej si môžete pridať obľúbené stanice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Создайте собственную библиотеку, в которую можно добавлять любимые станции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Creați-vă propria bibliotecă unde puteți adăuga stațiile favorite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Crie sua própria biblioteca à qual você pode adicionar suas estações favoritas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Criar sua própria coleção onde pode adicionar suas estações favoritas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie własnej kolekcji, do której można dodawać ulubione stacje</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Creatz vòstra pròpria bibliotèca ont podètz apondre vòstras estacions favoritas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Maak uw eigen collectie aan en voeg uw favoriete radiostations eraan toe</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">შექმენით თქვენი საკუთარი ბიბლიოთეკა, სადაც შეგიძლიათ თქვენი საყვარელი სადგურები დაამატოთ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Creare una propria raccolta dove poter aggiungere le stazioni preferite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Búðu til eigin lista sem þú getur bætt í uppáhalds-stöðvunum þínum</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Buat perpustakaan Anda sendiri di mana Anda dapat menambahkan stasiun favorit Anda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Crea tu proprie bibliotheca ubi tu pote adder tu stationes favorite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Saját könyvtár létrehozása, ahol hozzáadhatja a kedvenc állomásait</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Stvorite svoju vlastitu radioteku gdje možete dodati svoje omiljene stanice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">अपनी खुद की लाइब्रेरी बनाएं जहां आप अपने पसंदीदा स्टेशन जोड़ सकें</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">יצירת ספרייה משלך אליה ניתן להוסיף את התחנות המועדפות עליך</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Cree a súa propia biblioteca onde engadir as súas emisoras favoritas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Creâ la tô librarie personâl, dulà che tu puedis zontâ lis tôs stazions preferidis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Créez votre propre bibliothèque où ajouter vos stations préférées</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Luo oma kirjasto, johon voit lisätä omat suosikkiasemasi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">ایجاد کتاب‌خانهٔ خودتان با توانایی افزودن ایستگاه‌های محبوبتان</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Sortu zure liburutegi propioa zure gogoko estazioak gehitzeko</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Crear su propia biblioteca donde puede añadir sus emisoras favoritas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Create your own library where you can add your favourite stations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Δημιουργήστε τη δική σας βιβλιοθήκη όπου μπορείτε να προσθέσετε τους αγαπημένους σας σταθμούς</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Erstellen Sie Ihre eigene Bibliothek, zu der Sie Ihre Lieblingssender hinzufügen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Opret dit eget bibliotek hvor du kan tilføje dine favoritstationer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Vytvoření vlastní knihovny, kam si můžete přidat oblíbené stanice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Crea la teva pròpia biblioteca on pots afegir les teves emissores preferides</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Може да създадете собствена библиотека, в която да добавите любимите си станции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Стварыце ўласную бібліятэку, куды будзеце дадаваць свае ўлюбёныя станцыі</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Shortwave/raw/main/data/screenshots/2.png</image>
      <caption>Easily search and discover new radio stations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">輕而易舉便能搜尋與探索新電臺</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">轻松搜索并发现新电台</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Dễ dàng tìm kiếm và khám phá các đài phát thanh mới</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Простий пошук і виявлення нових радіостанцій</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Yeni radyo istasyonlarını kolayca arayın ve keşfedin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Sök och upptäck enkelt nya radiostationer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Једноставна претрага и откривање нових радио станица</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Enostavno iskanje in odkrivanje novih radijskih postaj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Jednoducho vyhľadávajte a objavujte nové rádiové stanice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Легкий поиск и открытие новых радиостанций</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Căutați și descoperiți stații noi radio cu ușurință</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquise e descubra facilmente novas estações de rádio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Procurar facilmente e descobrir novas estações de rádio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Łatwe wyszukiwanie i odkrywanie nowych stacji radiowych</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Cercatz e descobrissètz aisidament de novèlas estacions de ràdio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Zoek en ontdek eenvoudig nieuwe radiostations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მარტივად მოძებნეთ და აღმოაჩინეთ ახალი რადიოსადგურები</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Cercare e scoprire facilmente nuove stazioni radio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Uppgötvaðu og leitaðu á auðveldan máta að nýjum útvarpsstöðvum</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Mudah mencari dan menemukan stasiun radio baru</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Cerca e discoperi nove stationes de radio facilemente</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Új rádióállomások egyszerű keresése és felfedezése</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Jednostavno pretražujte i otkrijte nove radio stanice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">नए रेडियो स्टेशन आसानी से खोजें और ढूंढें</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">חיפוש קל לגילוי תחנות רדיו חדשות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Busque e descubra facilmente novas emisoras de radio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Cirî e scuvierzi cun facilitât lis gnovis stazions radio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Cherchez et découvrez de nouvelles stations de radio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Etsi ja löydä vaivatta uusia radioasemia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">جست‌وجو و کشف آسان ایستگاه‌های رادیویی جدید</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Bilatu eta aurkitu irrati-estazio berriak modu errazean</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Buscar y descubrir nuevas emisoras de radio fácilmente</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Easily search and discover new radio stations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Εύκολη αναζήτηση και ανακάλυψη νέων ραδιοφωνικών σταθμών</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Einfaches Suchen und Entdecken neuer Radiosender</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Det er let at søge efter og opdage nye radiostationer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Snadné vyhledávání a objevování nových rádiových stanic</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Cerca fàcilment i descobreix emissores de ràdio noves</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Лесно търсене и откриване на нови радиостанции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Просты пошук і агляд новых радыёстанцый</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Shortwave/raw/main/data/screenshots/3.png</image>
      <caption>Responsive application layout, compatible for small and large screens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">響應式程式佈局，不論熒幕尺寸大小皆可相容</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">响应式应用程序布局，兼容小型屏幕和大型屏幕</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Bố cục ứng dụng thích ứng, tương thích với cả màn hình nhỏ và lớn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Якісне компонування вікна програми, яке сумісне із малими і великими екранами</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Küçük ve büyük ekranlarla uyumlu, duyarlı uygulama düzeni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Kvickt reagerande programlayout, kompatibel med små och stora skärmar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Изглед програма прилагодљив величини екрана, усклађен са малим и великим екранима</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Odzivno prilagajanje programa je skladno z velikimi in majhnimi zasloni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Dobre reagujúce rozloženie aplikácie, kompatibilné s malými aj veľkými obrazovkami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Отзывчивый интерфейс приложения, совместимый с маленькими и большими экранами</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Aspect de aplicație responsiv, compatibil cu ecrane mici și mari</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Leiaute de aplicativo responsivo, compatível com telas pequenas e grandes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Modelo de aplicação responsivo, compatível com ecrãs pequenos ou grandes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Interfejs zgodny z małymi i wielkimi ekranami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Disposicion d'aplicacion responsiva, compatibla amb d'ecrans pichons e grands</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Responsieve indeling, geschikt voor zowel kleine als grote schermen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">აპლიკაციის მოხერხებული განლაგება, თავსებადი მცირე და დიდ ეკრანებთან</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Una reattiva disposizione dell'applicazione, compatibile per schermi piccoli e grandi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Aðlaganlegt viðmót , samræmanlegt fyrir litla og stóra skjái</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tata letak aplikasi responsif, kompatibel untuk layar kecil dan besar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Disposition responsive de application, compatibile con schermos parve e grande</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Alkalmazkodó alkalmazáselrendezés, kis és nagy képernyők támogatása</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Odgovarajući izgled aplikacije, kompatibilan za male i velike zaslone</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">उत्तरदायी अनुप्रयोग अभिन्यास, छोटी और बड़ी स्क्रीन के लिए संगत</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">פריסת היישום משתנה ומגיבה, מתאימה למסכים קטנים וגדולים כאחד</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Disposición de aplicación responsiva, compatíbel con pantallas pequenas e grandes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Struture dal program adatabil, compatibil cui schermis piçui e grancj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Interface adaptative, compatible avec les petits et grands écrans</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Mukautuva sovelluksen asettelu, yhteensopiva pienien ja suurien näyttöjen kanssa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">چینش واکنشگرای برنامه،‌سازگار با صفحه‌های بزرگ و کوچک</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Aplikazio-diseinu moldagarria, pantaila txiki zein handiekin bateragarria dena</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Diseño adaptativo, compatible con pantallas grandes y pequeñas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Responsive application layout, compatible for small and large screens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Dynamisches Anwendungslayout, kompatibel mit kleinen und großen Bildschirmen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Programlayoutet tilpasser sig automatisk på både små og store skærme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Responzivní rozvržení aplikace kompatibilní s malými a velkými obrazovkami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Disposició d'aplicació responsiva, compatible amb pantalles grans i petites</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Потребителски интерфейс съвместим с малки и големи екрани</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Адаптыўны інтэрфейс праграмы, сумяшчальны з малымі і вялікімі экранамі</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <!-- Releases -->
  <releases>
    <release version="5.0.0" date="2025-02-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          Shortwave now supports background playback, allowing the playback to continue when you close the window. If desired, the old behaviour can be restored in the preferences.
        </p>
        <p>
          The recording feature has also been completely overhauled. You can now choose from three different modes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Save All Tracks: Automatically save all recorded tracks</li>
          <li>Decide for Each Track: Temporarily record tracks and save only the ones you want</li>
          <li>Record Nothing: Stations are played without recording</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Additional Recording Enhancements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Directory in which recorded tracks are saved can be changed</li>
          <li>Minimum and maximum duration of recorded tracks can be configured</li>
          <li>Tracks can already be marked to be saved during recording</li>
          <li>Ongoing recordings can be cancelled</li>
          <li>Improved desktop notifications, with the direct option to mark tracks to be saved</li>
          <li>New dialog window for tracks with detailed information</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Other Improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Volume can now be changed via keyboard shortcuts</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue which prevented station covers from loading in certain desktop environments</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.1" date="2024-10-18">
      <description>
        <p>
          App metadata / branding improvements
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2024-10-17">
      <description>
        <p>
          General
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">一般</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">常规</p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">Chung</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Загальні</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Genel</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Allmänt</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Опште</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Splošno</p>
        <p xml:lang="sk">Všeobecné</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Общие</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Generale</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Geral</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Geral</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Ogólne</p>
        <p xml:lang="oc">General</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Algemeen</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">მთავარი</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Generale</p>
        <p xml:lang="is">Almennt</p>
        <p xml:lang="id">Umum</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">General</p>
        <p xml:lang="hu">Általános</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Općenito</p>
        <p xml:lang="hi">सामान्य</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">כללי</p>
        <p xml:lang="gl">Xeral</p>
        <p xml:lang="fur">Gjenerâl</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Général</p>
        <p xml:lang="fi">Yleiset</p>
        <p xml:lang="fa">عمومی</p>
        <p xml:lang="eu">Orokorra</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">General</p>
        <p xml:lang="en-GB">General</p>
        <p xml:lang="el">Γενικά</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Allgemein</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Generelt</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Obecné</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">General</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Общи</p>
        <p xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Агульныя</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New MPRIS media controls implementation with improved CPU usage</li>
          <li>Song notifications are disabled by default now</li>
          <li>Refreshed user interface by making use of new Libadwaita widgets</li>
          <li>Large parts of the app were reworked, providing a solid foundation for the next upcoming features</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Playback
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">回放</p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">Phát lại</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Відтворення</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Kayıttan Yürüt</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Uppspelning</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr-Cyrl">Репродукција</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Predvajanje</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Воспроизведение</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Redare</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Reprodução</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Reproduzir</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzanie</p>
        <p xml:lang="oc">Lectura</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Afspelen</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">დაკვრა</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Riproduzione</p>
        <p xml:lang="is">Afspilun</p>
        <p xml:lang="id">Putar</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">Reproduction</p>
        <p xml:lang="hu">Lejátszás</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Reprodukcija</p>
        <p xml:lang="hi">प्लेबैक</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">ניגון</p>
        <p xml:lang="gl">Reprodución</p>
        <p xml:lang="fur">Riprodûs</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Lecture</p>
        <p xml:lang="fi">Toisto</p>
        <p xml:lang="fa">پخش</p>
        <p xml:lang="eu">Erreproduzitu</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Reproducción</p>
        <p xml:lang="en-GB">Playback</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Wiedergabe</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Afspilning</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Přehrávání</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Reproducció</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Възпроизвеждане</p>
        <p xml:lang="be-Cyrl">Прайграванне</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Last station now gets restored on app launch</li>
          <li>Redesigned player sidebar, allowing to control volume more easily</li>
          <li>New recording indicator showing whether the current playback is being recorded</li>
          <li>Fixed buffering issue which prevented playing new stations, especially after switching stations too fast</li>
          <li>Fixed issues which sometimes prevented that a song gets recorded</li>
          <li>Fixed issue that volume remains muted after unmuting</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Library
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">Thư viện</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Bibliotecă</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Biblioteca</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Kolekcja</p>
        <p xml:lang="is">Safn</p>
        <p xml:lang="id">Pustaka</p>
        <p xml:lang="hu">Könyvtár</p>
        <p xml:lang="hi">लाइब्रेरी</p>
        <p xml:lang="gl">Biblioteca</p>
        <p xml:lang="fur">Librarie</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Knihovna</p>
        <ul>
          <li>No more loading on startup, stations now get directly retrieved from cached data</li>
          <li>Fixed issue which sometimes prevented loading more than 8 stations from library</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Station Covers
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>More supported image file format for station covers</li>
          <li>Enhanced security by loading station covers using sandboxed Glycin image library</li>
          <li>Non square covers automatically get a blurred background</li>
          <li>New generated fallback for stations without any cover image</li>
          <li>Improved disk usage by automatically purging no longer needed cached data</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Browse / Search
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>More useful station suggestions by respecting configured system language / region</li>
          <li>Suggestions now get updated with every start, no longer always showing the same stations</li>
          <li>More accessible search feature, no longer hidden in a subpage</li>
          <li>Search results are no longer limited at 250 stations</li>
          <li>Faster and more efficient search by using new grid widgets</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Chromecast
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Shortwave is now a registered Google Cast app, no longer relying on the generic media player</li>
          <li>New backend which greatly improves communication stability with cast devices</li>
          <li>Improved discovery of cast devices with lower CPU and memory usage</li>
          <li>Now possible to change the volume of a connected cast device</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2023-02-07">
      <description>
        <p>
          This version includes minor improvements and bug fixes.
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Small user interface improvements</li>
          <li>App can now be closed with CTRL+W</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.0" date="2022-10-15">
      <description>
        <p>
          This version includes minor improvements and bug fixes.
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Small user interface improvements</li>
          <li>Use new Adwaita about dialog</li>
          <li>Fixed a crash when the "Music" directory is not available</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0.0" date="2022-04-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          Version 3.0.0 is a stable release, with the following major
          improvements since 2.0.1:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated user interface that uses the new Adwaita design, with many improvements.</li>
          <li>Support for the new GNOME 42 dark mode.</li>
          <li>New option to add private stations to the library, which should not (or cannot) be available on radio-browser.info (e.g. local network or paid streams).</li>
          <li>Display station bitrate information, which can also be used as a sorting option.</li>
          <li>Save station data to disk so that it is still available when a station gets removed from the online database.</li>
          <li>New button on the search page that allows to sort the search results.</li>
          <li>Overhauled station dialog, with more clearly displayed information.</li>
          <li>Update desktop notification on song change instead of generating a new separate notification for each song.</li>
          <li>Shortwave can now be used normally, even if radio-browser.info is offline / unavailable.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Besides these improvements, this version also includes many changes
          under the hood changes, so many crashes and other bugs have been
          fixed. It also contains updated translations for 31 different
          languages.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.0.1" date="2021-04-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          This version contains minor improvements and bug fixes.
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improve buffering to avoid audio issues for streams with a high bitrate.</li>
          <li>Fix issue that no connection could be established when a VPN connection was active.</li>
          <li>Automatically select search entry when the search view gets activated.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.0.0" date="2021-03-10">
      <description>
        <p>
          Version 2.0.0 is a stable release, with the following major
          improvements since 1.1.0:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Get notified about new songs via desktop notifications.</li>
          <li>New mini player window mode. Control important features with a super compact window widget.</li>
          <li>Redesigned station information dialog window. Added ability to copy the stream url.</li>
          <li>Improved keyboard navigation of the user interface.</li>
          <li>Inhibit sleep/hibernate mode during audio playback.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          Besides these improvements, this version contains many under the hood
          changes. The complete user interface has been updated from GTK3 to
          GTK4. Many app components have been modernised or completely
          rewritten. As a result, many crashes or other bugs have been fixed.
        </p>
        <p>
          This version also contains updated translations for 27 different
          languages.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.1" date="2020-06-07">
      <description>
        <p>This version fixes a bug that caused some users not to be able to record songs.</p>
        <p>This release also updates translations in several languages.</p>
        <p>
          This might be the last release with the feature to import Gradio
          databases. The needed API server will be deactivated / no longer
          available in August 2020.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2020-06-01">
      <description>
        <p>
          Version 1.1.0 is a stable release, with the following major
          improvements since 1.0.1:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add CTRL + spacebar as shortcut to start/stop audio playback.</li>
          <li>Add stream buffering to prevent playback stuttering.</li>
          <li>Add featured carousel to discover page.</li>
          <li>Add support for non pulseaudio systems / environments.</li>
          <li>Add support for additional mouse buttons to switch between views.</li>
          <li>Improve stability of audio/recording backend.</li>
          <li>Fixed issue that the volume didn't get calculated correctly (linear/cubic).</li>
          <li>Fixed issue that broken stations are getting displayed in search results.</li>
          <li>Fixed issue with random scrolling in search page.</li>
          <li>Fixed issues which prevented to import Gradio databases.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations in several languages.</p>
        <p>
          This might be the last release with the feature to import Gradio
          databases. The needed API server will be deactivated / no longer
          available in August 2020.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2020-03-15">
      <description>
        <p>Fixes a bug that no songs can be saved.</p>
        <p>Add Finnish translation.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2020-03-14">
      <description>
        <p>First stable release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.0.3" date="2020-03-08">
      <description>
        <p>Third beta release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.0.2" date="2020-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>Second beta release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.0.1" date="2019-11-09">
      <description>
        <p>First beta release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
